

Contact

Phone

+02-01116798122

Address

Qalyubia / Al Qanater El Khayreya

Email

hamdymedo525@gmail.com

Portfolio

https://mohamed22221.github.io/M ohamed

Github

https://github.com/Mohamed2222 1?tab=repositories

Linkedin

https://www.linkedin.com/in/moha med-al-asfar-94b992219/

Skills

Html/Html5

Css/Css3

Javascript

Bootstrap

React.js

Redux/toolkit

NEXT.JS

BOOTSTRAP REACT

STYLED-COMPONENTS

MATERIAL UI GIT/GITHUBUI

Mohamed Hamdy

Front-End React

About Me

junior front-end React developer with 2+ years of experience designing and building responsive web design, Proficient with CSS and JS Frameworks, with extensive knowledge of UX and user psychology. Notable achievements include boosting the conversion rate of an existing website by 90% with improved code and design

Educational

2020 - 2022

Ain shams university

Faculty of Commerce

2017 - 2019

azhar el delta school

High school

Experiences

17/1/2022 - 20/1/2022

mostagl.com

Marketing product landing page

10/1/2022 - 14/1/2022

Dashboard

Created with only React.js, css3, material ui

4/1/2022 - 8/1/2022

<u>cryptocurrency</u>

Created with only React.js , css3 ,Axios Api , material ui

25/12/2021 - 28/12/2021

<u>Landing page color</u>

Created with only React.js/ css3 and bootstrap

20/12/2021 - 22/12/2021

calculator

Created with only React.js/css3 and bootstrap

7/7/2021 - 11/7/2021

Gym prodact

Created using HTML/CSS/javascript/bootstrap